

CONTACT

7020860045, 9421831705mr.rushikeshkakade14@gm



Pune, Maharashtra, India

EDUCATION

2012 - 2016 SINHGAD INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

• B.E Computer Science

SKILLS

- Project Management
- Public Relations
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Leadership
- Effective Communication
- Problem Solving
- Decision Making

LANGUAGES

- Marathi (Fluent)
- Hindi (Fluent)
- English (Fluent)

RUSHIKESH KAKADE

CLOSING MANAGER

PROFILE

Real Estate Manager With 3+ Years Of Residential & Commercial Sales Experience Within The Pune City. Expert In Planning & Interacting New Customer. Also Expert In Market Research, Negotiation, Customer Analysis, Deal Closing, Project Pitching, Lead Generation, Customer Handling etc.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sai Prerana Group Of Companies (June 2023 - Present)

Closing Manager

- · Closing Deals.
- Price Negotiation.
- · Lead Generation.
- · Maintain Client Relationships.
- Responsible for sales and marketing of the residential site through all verticals.
- Team Management.

Square Yards (March 2022 - May 2023)

Senior Investment Manager

- Client acquisition and business development by direct/indirect sales.
- Maximize revenue generation and lead closures by using social and public media marketing campaigns.
- Strong client focus including pre and post sales services for long term wealth retention.
- Meet and advise clients on real estate.

S.K. Associates (Jan 2021 - Jan 2022)

Investment Manager

- Set up meetings with potential clients and listen to their wishes and concerns
- Prepare and deliver appropriate presentations on products and services.

ICICI Bank Personal Loan (Jan 2020- Dec 2020)

Investment Manager

- Set up meetings with potential clients and listen to their wishes and concerns.
- Prepare and deliver appropriate presentations on products and services.